<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="s_atawah_about" name="Atawah About">
        <section id="about" class="s_atawah_about pt96 pb96" data-snippet="s_atawah_about" data-name="Atawah About">
            <div class="container">
                <div class="row align-items-start gy-5">
                    <div class="col-lg-6">
                        <span class="atawah_eyebrow_tag">About Atawa</span>
                        <h2>Where financial expertise meets digital transformation</h2>
                        <p class="atawah_lead_text">
                            Atawa is a financial and digital consulting company dedicated to giving businesses in
                            Oman a smarter, more efficient way to manage their operations. We combine professional
                            accounting expertise with modern digital transformation technologies to deliver
                            intelligent, accurate and easy-to-use solutions that help companies grow confidently in
                            a fast-changing market.
                        </p>
                    </div>

                    <div class="col-lg-6">
                        <div class="atawah_feature_block">
                            <span class="atawah_eyebrow_tag">Our Vision</span>
                            <h3>Clarity over complexity</h3>
                            <p>
                                We turn financial complexity into clarity and transform traditional workflows into
                                digital systems that operate with higher efficiency and lower cost — becoming the
                                trusted partner companies rely on throughout their journey toward a fully integrated
                                digital future.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="atawah_feature_block">
                            <span class="atawah_eyebrow_tag">Our Mission</span>
                            <h3>Simple, accurate, real results</h3>
                            <p>
                                To make digital transformation accessible, simple and effective for every business
                                — while delivering financial services built on accuracy, transparency and
                                measurable outcomes.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>

                <div class="atawah_section_head atawah_section_head_mt">
                    <span class="atawah_eyebrow_tag">What we deliver</span>
                    <h3>Five pillars, one integrated partner</h3>
                    <p>Engineered to work together — finance, data and ERP under a single team.</p>
                </div>

                <div class="atawah_pillars_grid">
                    <div class="atawah_pillar_card">
                        <h4>Digital Accounting</h4>
                        <p>Accurate financial management, real-time reporting and integrated accounting systems.</p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="atawah_pillar_card">
                        <h4>Digital Transformation</h4>
                        <p>Workflow automation, process optimization and seamless system integration.</p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="atawah_pillar_card">
                        <h4>ERP Implementation</h4>
                        <p>Unified operational environments that empower faster, smarter decision-making.</p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="atawah_pillar_card">
                        <h4>Odoo Solutions</h4>
                        <p>Customization, setup and development tailored to each business.</p>
                    </div>
                    <div class="atawah_pillar_card">
                        <h4>Financial Consulting</h4>
                        <p>Strategic guidance, financial planning and performance analysis.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </section>
    </template>
</odoo>
